flashtool.org 2018-06-03

# Privacy Policy - FlashTool

## Privacy and Cookies Policy

At FlashTool.org, we respect the privacy of our visitors!

By visiting this website, you automatically agree with the collection and use of information in the manner described here.

Occasionally, if prescribed by law, you may be asked to provide your consent for the processing of certain data and information that has been collected on this website or which you yourself have provided.

At FlashTool Team, your privacy is our number one concern. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by FlashTool.org (The Site) and how it is used.

## Personal Information

FlashTool.org does not require any information which can be traced back to, and identify a unique user. Certain features of the site however (like comments for example) , do require a valid email address to verify legitimate users. We guarantee that the information provided to The Site would never be used for any other purpose.

## Log Files

Like many other web sites, FlashTool Team makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. All of the data recorded is not linked to any information that could personally identify a unique individual.

## What Are Cookies:

As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or �break� certain elements of the site�s functionality. For more general information on cookies see the Wikipedia article on HTTP Cookies.

## Cookies and Web Beacons:-

This site itself, does not use any cookies to store information. Third party service providers however may store information on your computer. Refer to the following sections to understand what information is collected and how to opt out of the process.

## \- DISQUS Comments

FlashTool Team uses Disqus Comments system to collect and manage comments on the blog. Disqus, as a third party service provider uses cookies to maintain your Disqus profile. You may easily opt out of the process by not posting a comment on the site.

## \- DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on FlashTool.org.
  * Google�s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to FlashTool.org and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies

## **Third Party Cookies** :

In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.

This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.

For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.  
Third party analytics are used to track and measure usage of this site so that we can continue to produce engaging content. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site or pages you visit which helps us to understand how we can improve the site for you.

The Google AdSense service we use to serve advertising uses a DoubleClick cookie to serve more relevant ads across the web and limit the number of times that a given ad is shown to you.

For more information on Google AdSense see the official Google AdSense privacy FAQ.

We use adverts to offset the costs of running this site and provide funding for further development. The behavioral advertising cookies used by this site are designed to ensure that we provide you with the most relevant adverts where possible by anonymously tracking your interests and presenting similar things that may be of interest.

## Policy Changes

Flashtool.org reserves the right to make any (major or minor) change to this privacy document without any prior warning. The site may or may not notify the users regarding any change made to the policy, however we will always reflect the latest policies and their effective dates in this document.

## Further Information

If you require any further information about the policy or clarification on any of the clauses, please feel free to contact http://flashtool.org/p/contact.html.
